Guide to the PricewaterhouseCoopers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Coopers & Lybrand Series III: Photographs
  - Subseries III.2: B&W Negatives Collection
    - Sub-subseries III.2.1: 35 mm negative strips
      - 75096 - [Lybrand Journal - Construction], [1969], 13 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - 75184 - [Barnes Cordova and Eley Moving Storage], 28 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - 75455 - Senior Audit Course; Lybrand Journal - Job Workshop, 1969, 235 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - 75986-1 - Partners' Meeting, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - 76107 - Executive Committee, 146 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - 76347-1 - New York Relocation, 25 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - 76347-2 - [unidentified man at desk], 8 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - 370368 - Supervisory Personnel - Managers, Feb. 1974, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - 392255 - Supervisory Personnel - New York, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - 400232 - Tax Library, 90 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - 400571 - Mr. [Daniole], 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - 401028-2 - Heit, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - 401941 - Merchandizing, Retailing, 72 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - 402278 - Burke, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - 402345 - C&L International Meeting, New York Hilton, Sep. 1969, 318 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - 402631 - Open House, White Plains, NY, Sep. 1969, 172 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - 402759 - Directory - Broadway, 13 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - 402783 - Mr. McCarthy, 12 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - 403282 - [Mets Celebration], 168 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - 403651 - Audit Management Meeting, NJ, 1969, 74 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - 403903 - Mr. Schain, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - 403973 - [unidentified man], 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - 403977 - Merridith Sengstocke, 32 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - 404913 - Vituli, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - 405277 - [inidentified event], 33 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - 406001 - Varner, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - 407994 - Philip Defliese, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - 408311 - Stu Singer, 3 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - 409175-1 - Feve, Jean-Louis; New CPA's, 1970, 92 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - 410218 - Felix Pomeranz (partner) - Candid photos, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - 411207 - Slide Show: [Admission Laboratiory Work Flow Cash Study], 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - 413809-1 - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office, 108 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - 415012 - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office, 72 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - 415160 - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office, 33 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - 415250 - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - 415260 - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - 415381 - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office, 28 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 415484-A - Peter Watt - Lybrand Journal Candids, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 415484-B - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 415634 - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office, 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 416882 - S. Singer and I. Forsyth - Lybrand Journal, 1971, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 417441 - Construction Contractors Workshop - Lybrand Journal, 29 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 417483 - Recruit Orientation, NY Practice Office - A. Rua, 19 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 427799 - J. J. Mahon - Candid Pictures, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 428020 - J. Meredith, W.A. Mithcell, W.T. Barnes, Mar. 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 428323 - Staff Athletic Activities, 72 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 428659-1 - Personnel Photos - Supervisors, 46 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 428281-1 - Personnel Photos - Supervisors, 54 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - 429286 - P&L House Journal Name Contest: Choosing, Winner Photos, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 429683 - Brian Tallon - Candid Podium Photos, Apr. 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 430128-1 - Professional Activities - CPA Dinner; Lybrand College Contributions, 26427, 55 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 430218 - National Training Module Photos, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 430329 - Personnel Photos - Supervisors, 1972, 40 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 430453 - Personnel Photos - Supervisors, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 430454 - NY Office Staff Outing, 26420, 60 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 431112- C.W. Post Audit Staff Training Photos, 160 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 431216 - William Mitchell Photo. Q&A - Lybrand Journal, Vol. 53, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - 431605 - New Mechanism of Government - Lybrand Journal, Vol. 53, 1972, 144 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 431675 - Personnel Photos - Supervisors, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 431948 - Lybrand Journal: Steering the V.A.T. - J. Scripps - Retail Copper Products Photos, 1972, 14 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 432070 - Tax and Management Seminar, Room 422, 1972, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 432158 - Brick Walls - Lybrand Journal Feature, Vol. 53, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 432195 - Personnel Photos - Supervisors, 1972, 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 432212 - Louis H. Rappaport - Lybrand Journal Feature Photos, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 432213 - Personnel Photos - Supervisors, 1972, 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 432458 - Personnel Photos - Supervisors, 1972, 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - 432615 - Partners and Principals Directory: J. Matthews-R. Murray-J. Fox, 1972, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 432977 - L. Anderson - Partner, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 433069 - [Leasing vs. Buying Guide], 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 433069 - Bulletin Photo Illustrating Redesigned Journal, Oct. 1972, 13 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 433434 - Julian Phelps, Sep. 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 433593 - Social Introduction of New Merger Partners Frogge & Diu, 1972, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 434194 - Bulletin Photos - Internal Computer Operations, Oct. 1972, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 434353 - Bulletin Photos - Internal Computer Operations, Oct. 1972, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 434478 - United Fund Chairmen G. McQueen & M. Markendorf, 1973, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 434979 - Cover Photos For the Insurance Industry Monograph, 1973, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 435041 - Cover Photos For the Insurance Industry Monograph, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - 435193 - James E. McKinney Publicity Candid Photos, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - 435759 - P&L Photo - Christmas Tree & Menorah, 1972, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - 435898 - P&L Photos, 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - 436272 - A. Sapega Photos - Lybrand Journal Feature, Rockford, IL, Dec. 1972, 104 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - 436328 - Supervisory Personnel Photos - Candid, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - 439167 - Supervisory Personnel, 1973, 6 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - 441144 - Supervisory Personnel, 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - 441509 - Supervisory Personnel and Richard Pagan, 10 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 441523 - Profile- New Managers, Oct. 1973, 10 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 442338 - Supervisory Personnel, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 442800 - Supervisory Personnel, 1973, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 443785 - Profile Photos of National Library and Equipment, Dec. 1973, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 444083 - Supervisory Personnel, Dec. 1973, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 444624 - Intern Meetings, Dec. 1973, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 445093 - Journal Award Bulletin, 1973, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 445179 - A. Krupa Birthday Party, Jan. 1974, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 446678 - Bulletin - PanAm - AuditPak Courses, 1974, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 447095 - NY State CPA Banquet - candid photos, 1974, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 448164 - R. Steinberg Candid Photos, 1975, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 448486 - S. Halperin & R. Steinberg Candid photos, Jul. 1974, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 449169 - Managers, Jul. 1974, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 449288 - Supervisory Personnel, 11 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 449418 - N.E.R. MCS Personnel, 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 449451 - Supervisory Personnel, 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 449478 - Philip Defliese - candid photos, Nov. 1974, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 449685 - Personnel Photos - Tax Dept. Managers, recently promoted, 1975, 10 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 450001 - R. Kirk Batzer and Dr. Mahesh Jain, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 450134 - NY National Office, New Building - Rockefeller Center, 30 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 450274 - NY National Office, New Building - Rockefeller Center - Interiors, Jul. 2, 1971, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 450390 - R. Kirk Batzer, Jul. 20, 1971, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 450394-1 - Sy Jones, Leo Tin, Mort Meyerson, Ron Burroughs - Bulletin, Jul. 1975, 12 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 450394-2 - N.E.R. MCS Personnel: Tom Bell (frames 3-6), Stanley Makadok (frames 7-9), 7 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 450573 - Faculty Interns Training, 1971, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 451310 - F. Sloat Ritirement and Birthday Photos, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 451358 - Lybrand Journal, 1971, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 451442 - Lybrand Journal, 1971, 17 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 451456 - Lybrand Journal, 1971, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 451496 - Executive [Bulletin] - Louis Moscarello - Bottger & Bolz, 1971, 25 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 451682 - New NY National Office at Rockefeller Center, 40 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 451682 - International Tax Conference, Plaza Hotel, Apr. 14, 1971, 30 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 451884 - Alan Vituli - Tax Staff, 13 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 451944 - Jack I. Epstein - Author Bio, Photos, 1971, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 451956 - V.M. Martinelli - Office Candids, 1971, 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 452861 - AA & SEC - Wm. McHugh, partner, Feb. 1976, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 453349 - MSC Personnel, 1976, 10 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 453520 - Bulletin photos: Sy Jones, Norman Auerbach, Kamen, N. Meyerson, R. Hackman, Jan. 1976, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 453599 - Bulletin photos: M. Baris, H. Danker - Public Relations, 1976, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 453914 - MSC Personnel, 1976, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 454192 - Wm. McHugh, partner, Mar. 1976, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 454865 - Bulletin, 1976, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 455086 - MSC Personnel, 1976, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - 455233 - NY Supervisory Personnel, 27881, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 455292 - Bulletin: H. Freidman, partner, R. Thylin, partner, both shown with associates, 60 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 457807 - Partners and Principals Directory: Felix Pomeranz - Partner, 1976, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 459459 - N.E.R. - MSC Personnel, 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 460223 - Bulletin - INSCO - Actuarial Group, 1974, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 461059 - M. Shegola - passport Photos, Sep. 1974, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 461613 - MSC Personnel - Candid Photos, 1975, 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 461773 - Office Personnel Candid Photos, White Plains, NY, 1975, 40 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 462332 - L. Bernstein, Mar. 1975, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 479495 - R. Colegrove, partner - Candid Photos, 1978, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 480103 - Charles R. Caulson Kurt, Apr. 1978, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 480366 - Staff Enternainment [athletic activities], 75 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 6833 - Training Program, Drew University, 1968, 13 (35 mm color negatives) (Box 30, Folder 67)
      - 30036 - Advanced Audit Course, Jul. 1968, 32 (35 mm color negatives) (Box 30, Folder 67)
    - Sub-subseries III.2.2: 4 x 5 negatives
      Slide shows for training courses: EDP (electronic data processing), auditing and taxation, workflow. 20 slides per negative. Some duplicates in separate folder
      - Nos: 1 - 9480. Missing: 3200-3220, 3981-4000, 6361-6380, 8241-9000, 9381-9400 (Box 30, Folder 68 - 81)
  - Subseries III.3: Event Photos
    - Sub-subseries III.3.1: Albums
      prints and some negatives of various C&L events, 1960s-1970s
      - LRB&M Girls Christmas Party, n.d., 5 (2.5 x 3.5 color negatives) (Box 30, Folder 82)
      - LRB&M Album E - [unidentified conference]. LRB&M employees from various US offices, many wearing name/city tags. Not indexed., n.d., 29 (8x10 b&w prints), 11 (8x10 color prints) (Box 30, Folder 83 - 85)
      - LRB&M 50th Anniversary Dinner. Name identifications on back of photos. Not indexed. Arranged by photo number (1 - 61, # 51, 52 missing), [1948], 59 (5 x 7 b&w prints) (Box 30, Folder 86)
      - LRB&M [New York Office] Outing, [Montclair Golf Club]. No names., Montclair, NJ, Jun. 6, 1960, 34 (8x10 b&w prints) (Box 31, Folder 1 - 3)
        [curled]
      - LRB&M Alumni Outing. Some name tags. Not indexed, Jun. 27, 1960, 59 (8x10 b&w prints) (Box 31, Folder 4 - 8)
      - LRB&M Quarter Century Club Banquet, Oct. 27, 1960, 4 (8x10 b&w prints) (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - LRB&M New York Office Outing, Montclair Golf Club. No names., Montclair, NJ, Jun. 6, 1961, 32 (8x10 b&w prints) (Box 31, Folder 10 - 12)
      - LRB&M Alumni Outing. Some name tags. Not indexed, Jun. 26, 1961, 45 (8x10 b&w prints), 2 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 13 - 16)
      - LRB&M Firm Tax Conference. Some name tags (mostly illegible). Not indexed, Oct. 9-11, 1961, 31 (8x10 b&w prints), 1 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 17 - 19)
      - C&L International Partners' Meeting. Name identifications on back of photos. Not indexed. Arranged by photo number (9 - 64, many missing). Routing slip enclosed., New York, NY, 1962, 45 (8x10 b&w prints) (Box 31, Folder 20 - 22)
      - LRB&M [New York Office] Golf Outing, Montclair Golf Club. No names., Montclair, NJ, 28-May-62, 41 (8x10 b&w prints), 12 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 23 - 26)
      - LRB&M Alumni Outing, Ridgewood Country Club. Some name tags. Not indexed, Jun. 11, 1962, 26 (8x10 b&w prints), 15 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 27 - 29)
      - C&L Open House - Hotel Plaza. International, employees wear name/city tags. Not indexed., Sep. 23, 1962, 26 (8x10 b&w prints) (Box 31, Folder 30 - 31)
      - C&L Open House - Hotel Plaza. [Group at dinner table]. No names., Sep. 23, 1962, 1 (4 x 5 color transparency) (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - LRB&M Christmas Party. No names., Dec. 1962, 22 (8x10 b&w prints), 14 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 33 - 35)
      - LRB&M [New York Office] Golf Outing, Montclair Golf Club. Some name tags. Not indexed, Montclair, NJ, 27-May-63, 29 (8x10 b&w prints), 20 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 36 - 39)
      - LRB&M Alumni Outing, Ridgewood Country Club. Some name tags. Not indexed, Jun. 24, 1963, 35 (8x10 b&w prints), 10 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 40 - 43)
        [Minor water damage, curling and yellowing]
      - Christmas Party. No names., [New York, NY], Dec. 1963, 9 (8x10 b&w prints), 18 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 44 - 45)
      - LRB&M [New York Office] Golf Outing, Montclair Golf Club. Some name tags. Not indexed, Montclair, NJ, Jun. 1, 1964, 23 (8x10 b&w prints), 28 (8x10 color prints) (Box 31, Folder 46 - 49)
      - LRB&M Alumni Outing, Ridgewood Country Club. Name Identification glued to prints. Indexed., Jun. 22, 1964, 6 (8x10 b&w prints), 43 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 1 - 4)
      - LRB&M Christmas Party. Some name tags, not indexed., Dec. 1964, 33 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 5 - 7)
      - LRB&M [New York Office] Golf Outing, Montclair Golf Club. Some name tags. Not indexed, Montclair, NJ, 17-May-65, 45 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 8 - 11)
        [water damage]
      - LRB&M Alumni Outing. Name Identification glued to prints. Indexed. Jun. 28, 1965, 14 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 12)
        [47 additional 8x10 color prints have been removed due to major water damage and mold]
      - LRB&M Christmas Party. Name tags, not indexed. Arranged by photo number. Routing slip enclosed., Dec. 1965, 57 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 13 - 17)
      - LRB&M Christmas Party negatives, Dec. 1965, 57 (2.5 x 3.5 color negatives) (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - LRB&M [New York Office Golf Outing,] Some name tags. Not indexed, Jun. 1966, 57 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 19 - 23)
      - LRB&M Alumni Outing, Ridgewood Country Club. Name Identification glued to prints. Indexed., Jun. 27, 1966, 60 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 24 - 28)
      - LRB&M Christmas Party at The Coachman. Name tags, not indexed. Arranged by photo number. (#9,10 - missing) Routing slip enclosed., Dec. 20, 1966, 58 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 29 - 33)
      - LRB&M Christmas Party negatives, Dec. 20, 1966, 52 (2.5 x 3.5 color negatives) (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - Client Reception and Dinner. Identification on the back of photos, Boston, MA, 16-May-67, 62 (5 x 7 b&w prints) (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - LRB&M [New York Office Golf Outing,] Some name tags. Not indexed, Jun. 1967, 71 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 36 - 40)
      - LRB&M Alumni Outing. Name Identification glued to prints. Indexed., Jun. 26, 1967, 64 (8x10 color prints) (Box 32, Folder 41 - 45)
        [Many prints curled due to water damage. 17 additional 8x10 color prints (#15, 17, 21, 23, 25, 27, 32-37, 39, 49, 54, 55, 83) have been removed due to major water damage and mold]
      - LRB&M Tax Symposium. Name tags, not indexed., Nov. 1967, 48 (8x10 b&w prints), 7 (8x10 color prints) (Box 33, Folder 1 - 4)
      - LRB&M Christmas Party. Name tags, not indexed. Arranged by photo number.Routing slip enclosed., Dec. 1967, 66 (8x10 color prints) (Box 33, Folder 5 - 9)
      - LRB&M Christmas Party negatives, Downtown Athletic Club, Dec. [19], 1967, 74 (2.5 x 3.5 color negatives) (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - LRB&M [New York Office Golf Outing,] Name tags. Not indexed, [May-Jun. 1968], 90 (8x10 color prints) (Box 33, Folder 11 - 17)
        [Minor water damage on some prints. One additional 8x10 color prints have been removed due to major water damage and mold]
      - LRB&M [Alumni Outing,] Name tags. Not indexed, [Jun-Jul. 1968], 86 (8x10 color prints) (Box 33, Folder 18 - 24)
      - LRB&M Christmas Party negatives, [Dec. 1968], 44 (2.5 x 3.5 color negatives) (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - C&L Partners-In-Charge Conference, Boca Raton, FL, Nov. 6-8, 1974, 4 (8x10 b&w prints) (Box 33, Folder 26)
        [One of the prints replaced by photocopy. Original filed as Pht-076 (used for centennial). Memos enclosed.]
      - C&L Honoring Phil Defliese, The PresidentsYacht, NY, Sep. 9, 1977, 47 (35 mm color negatives) (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - C&L International Firm Meeting. Name tags, not indexed., Boston, MA, Oct. 1979, 128 (5 x 7color prints) (Box 33, Folder 28 - 31)
        [Photos glued to 8x10 cardboards and laminated.]
    - Sub-subseries III.3.2: Developed film rolls
      color prints and negatives of various C&L events, 1980s - 1990s
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 1 prints. Name tags, not indexed., n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 29 (4 x 6 b&w Prints) (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 1 negatives, n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 40 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 2 prints. Name tags, not indexed., n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 39 (4 x 6 b&w Prints) (Box 33, Folder 34)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 2 negatives, n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 37 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 33, Folder 35)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 3 prints. Name tags, not indexed., n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 40 (4 x 6 b&w Prints) (Box 33, Folder 36)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 3 negatives, n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 109 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 33, Folder 37)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 4 prints. Name tags, not indexed., n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 30 (4 x 6 b&w Prints) (Box 33, Folder 38)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 5 prints. Name tags, not indexed., n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 16 (4 x 6 b&w Prints) (Box 33, Folder 39)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 6 prints. Name tags, not indexed., n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 25 (4 x 6 b&w Prints) (Box 33, Folder 40)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 6 negatives, n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 29 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 33, Folder 41)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 7 prints. Name tags, not indexed., n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 27 (4 x 6 b&w Prints) (Box 33, Folder 42)
      - C&L Alumni Social Roll 7 negatives, n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 26 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 33, Folder 43)
      - C&L Unidentified event, n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 120 (35 mm color negatives) (Box 33, Folder 44)
      - C&L [Business Conference]. No names, n.d. [1980s - 1990s], 6 (4 x 6 b&w Prints) (Box 33, Folder 45)
      - C&L Summer Jobs For Youth Ceremony, 1986, 1 (8 x 10 b&w prints) (Box 33, Folder 46)
        [2 identical prints]
      - C&L Second Women Partners Leadership Conference, n.d. [1990s], 36 (35 mm color negatives), 1 (contact sheet) (Box 33, Folder 47)